{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290702658","data":{"timestamp":" 947290702657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 956a7f9f-3d05-43b9-9577-17e12982d2ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290751064","data":{"timestamp":" 947290751063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 956a7f9f-3d05-43b9-9577-17e12982d2ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290751213","data":{"timestamp":" 947290751213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 956a7f9f-3d05-43b9-9577-17e12982d2ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290775822","data":{"timestamp":" 947290775822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290782847","data":{"timestamp":" 947290782847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290786515","data":{"timestamp":" 947290786514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290793619","data":{"timestamp":" 947290793618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290798735","data":{"timestamp":" 947290798735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290805138","data":{"timestamp":" 947290805138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290810085","data":{"timestamp":" 947290810085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290816021","data":{"timestamp":" 947290816021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290823332","data":{"timestamp":" 947290823332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290828610","data":{"timestamp":" 947290828609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290835721","data":{"timestamp":" 947290835721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290841240","data":{"timestamp":" 947290841240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290845068","data":{"timestamp":" 947290845068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290851761","data":{"timestamp":" 947290851761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290863693","data":{"timestamp":" 947290863693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290871278","data":{"timestamp":" 947290871278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290875011","data":{"timestamp":" 947290875011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290880547","data":{"timestamp":" 947290880547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290884249","data":{"timestamp":" 947290884249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290889042","data":{"timestamp":" 947290889042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290895038","data":{"timestamp":" 947290895038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290898780","data":{"timestamp":" 947290898780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290902712","data":{"timestamp":" 947290902712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290906194","data":{"timestamp":" 947290906194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290911990","data":{"timestamp":" 947290911990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290916050","data":{"timestamp":" 947290916050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290921671","data":{"timestamp":" 947290921671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290925194","data":{"timestamp":" 947290925194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290930616","data":{"timestamp":" 947290930616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290934028","data":{"timestamp":" 947290934028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290937450","data":{"timestamp":" 947290937450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290943206","data":{"timestamp":" 947290943206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 69f878fa-cd5c-4207-a355-ae34433914cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290961065","data":{"timestamp":" 947290961065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290965618","data":{"timestamp":" 947290965618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290970112","data":{"timestamp":" 947290970112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290973957","data":{"timestamp":" 947290973957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290980136","data":{"timestamp":" 947290980136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290984443","data":{"timestamp":" 947290984442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290988049","data":{"timestamp":" 947290988049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290992030","data":{"timestamp":" 947290992030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947290998230","data":{"timestamp":" 947290998230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291004640","data":{"timestamp":" 947291004640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291008614","data":{"timestamp":" 947291008614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291012597","data":{"timestamp":" 947291012597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291016861","data":{"timestamp":" 947291016860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291020819","data":{"timestamp":" 947291020818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291024040","data":{"timestamp":" 947291024039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291027946","data":{"timestamp":" 947291027945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291032432","data":{"timestamp":" 947291032431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291039637","data":{"timestamp":" 947291039637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291043661","data":{"timestamp":" 947291043661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291047158","data":{"timestamp":" 947291047158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291052845","data":{"timestamp":" 947291052845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291056461","data":{"timestamp":" 947291056461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291060933","data":{"timestamp":" 947291060933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291065893","data":{"timestamp":" 947291065893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291069662","data":{"timestamp":" 947291069662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291072912","data":{"timestamp":" 947291072912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291078690","data":{"timestamp":" 947291078688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" ea575359-28f9-4f70-bcac-bd5ff8fba8d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291090460","data":{"timestamp":" 947291090460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291092565","data":{"timestamp":" 947291092564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291094732","data":{"timestamp":" 947291094731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291097971","data":{"timestamp":" 947291097970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291100232","data":{"timestamp":" 947291100231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291102500","data":{"timestamp":" 947291102499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291105333","data":{"timestamp":" 947291105333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291107555","data":{"timestamp":" 947291107554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291109753","data":{"timestamp":" 947291109752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291113026","data":{"timestamp":" 947291113025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291115145","data":{"timestamp":" 947291115144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291117269","data":{"timestamp":" 947291117269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291120309","data":{"timestamp":" 947291120308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291122557","data":{"timestamp":" 947291122556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291124753","data":{"timestamp":" 947291124752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291127804","data":{"timestamp":" 947291127803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291130168","data":{"timestamp":" 947291130168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291132549","data":{"timestamp":" 947291132548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291135628","data":{"timestamp":" 947291135627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291137793","data":{"timestamp":" 947291137792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291139938","data":{"timestamp":" 947291139938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291143060","data":{"timestamp":" 947291143060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291145254","data":{"timestamp":" 947291145253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291147453","data":{"timestamp":" 947291147453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291150627","data":{"timestamp":" 947291150626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291153065","data":{"timestamp":" 947291153064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291155503","data":{"timestamp":" 947291155502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291158650","data":{"timestamp":" 947291158649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291160931","data":{"timestamp":" 947291160930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291163221","data":{"timestamp":" 947291163220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291166228","data":{"timestamp":" 947291166228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291168461","data":{"timestamp":" 947291168460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291170677","data":{"timestamp":" 947291170676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291173680","data":{"timestamp":" 947291173680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291176084","data":{"timestamp":" 947291176084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291178452","data":{"timestamp":" 947291178451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291181620","data":{"timestamp":" 947291181619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291183985","data":{"timestamp":" 947291183984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291186376","data":{"timestamp":" 947291186376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291189363","data":{"timestamp":" 947291189363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291191679","data":{"timestamp":" 947291191678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291193976","data":{"timestamp":" 947291193975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291197232","data":{"timestamp":" 947291197231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291199516","data":{"timestamp":" 947291199516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291201773","data":{"timestamp":" 947291201772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291205166","data":{"timestamp":" 947291205165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291207624","data":{"timestamp":" 947291207623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291210106","data":{"timestamp":" 947291210105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291213028","data":{"timestamp":" 947291213027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291215243","data":{"timestamp":" 947291215242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291217456","data":{"timestamp":" 947291217455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291220905","data":{"timestamp":" 947291220904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291223265","data":{"timestamp":" 947291223263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291225580","data":{"timestamp":" 947291225580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291228702","data":{"timestamp":" 947291228701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291230962","data":{"timestamp":" 947291230961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291233254","data":{"timestamp":" 947291233253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291236328","data":{"timestamp":" 947291236327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291238475","data":{"timestamp":" 947291238474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291240612","data":{"timestamp":" 947291240611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291243767","data":{"timestamp":" 947291243765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291246046","data":{"timestamp":" 947291246045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291248306","data":{"timestamp":" 947291248305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291251596","data":{"timestamp":" 947291251594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291253842","data":{"timestamp":" 947291253842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291256080","data":{"timestamp":" 947291256080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291259364","data":{"timestamp":" 947291259364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291261728","data":{"timestamp":" 947291261727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291264068","data":{"timestamp":" 947291264067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291267196","data":{"timestamp":" 947291267196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291269539","data":{"timestamp":" 947291269538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291271916","data":{"timestamp":" 947291271915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291275357","data":{"timestamp":" 947291275355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291275477","data":{"timestamp":" 947291275477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291324580","data":{"timestamp":" 947291324579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 34aed9d5-e1ca-473f-bc37-914a217731c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291338177","data":{"timestamp":" 947291338177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 3916b479-7510-450a-86a0-0ed0f2f6f761"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291390932","data":{"timestamp":" 947291390932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 3916b479-7510-450a-86a0-0ed0f2f6f761"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291391018","data":{"timestamp":" 947291391018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 3916b479-7510-450a-86a0-0ed0f2f6f761"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291411528","data":{"timestamp":" 947291411528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291411901","data":{"timestamp":" 947291411901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291412384","data":{"timestamp":" 947291412384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291412727","data":{"timestamp":" 947291412727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291413142","data":{"timestamp":" 947291413141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291413262","data":{"timestamp":" 947291413262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291413351","data":{"timestamp":" 947291413351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 64ef7f8b-75a8-43cd-bc1a-b7b89b7e21d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291434780","data":{"timestamp":" 947291434779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291437569","data":{"timestamp":" 947291437569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291439117","data":{"timestamp":" 947291439117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291442912","data":{"timestamp":" 947291442912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291444462","data":{"timestamp":" 947291444462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291447848","data":{"timestamp":" 947291447847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291449451","data":{"timestamp":" 947291449450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291453350","data":{"timestamp":" 947291453350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291454960","data":{"timestamp":" 947291454959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291458156","data":{"timestamp":" 947291458156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291459777","data":{"timestamp":" 947291459776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291462409","data":{"timestamp":" 947291462409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291464006","data":{"timestamp":" 947291464005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" NANASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291466532","data":{"timestamp":" 947291466530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" NANASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291468136","data":{"timestamp":" 947291468134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291473675","data":{"timestamp":" 947291473674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291475243","data":{"timestamp":" 947291475243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291478893","data":{"timestamp":" 947291478893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291480453","data":{"timestamp":" 947291480452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291480477","data":{"timestamp":" 947291480477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291483471","data":{"timestamp":" 947291483471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291485126","data":{"timestamp":" 947291485126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291486699","data":{"timestamp":" 947291486698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291489416","data":{"timestamp":" 947291489415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291491018","data":{"timestamp":" 947291491018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291493338","data":{"timestamp":" 947291493337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291494957","data":{"timestamp":" 947291494957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291497356","data":{"timestamp":" 947291497355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291498942","data":{"timestamp":" 947291498942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyumba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291501940","data":{"timestamp":" 947291501940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyumba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291503539","data":{"timestamp":" 947291503538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291506058","data":{"timestamp":" 947291506057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291507676","data":{"timestamp":" 947291507675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291510190","data":{"timestamp":" 947291510189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291511817","data":{"timestamp":" 947291511816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291517153","data":{"timestamp":" 947291517152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291518779","data":{"timestamp":" 947291518779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291524207","data":{"timestamp":" 947291524206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nguo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291525809","data":{"timestamp":" 947291525808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" NZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291528045","data":{"timestamp":" 947291528045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" NZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291529651","data":{"timestamp":" 947291529650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291532861","data":{"timestamp":" 947291532861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nywele"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291534494","data":{"timestamp":" 947291534493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291537092","data":{"timestamp":" 947291537091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291539119","data":{"timestamp":" 947291539118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291539246","data":{"timestamp":" 947291539246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" a863d7ca-29a1-401d-a7a2-6f3c76a4d5fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291552946","data":{"timestamp":" 947291552945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291555347","data":{"timestamp":" 947291555347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291556971","data":{"timestamp":" 947291556970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291562559","data":{"timestamp":" 947291562559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291564154","data":{"timestamp":" 947291564154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291573987","data":{"timestamp":" 947291573986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291575561","data":{"timestamp":" 947291575560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291580698","data":{"timestamp":" 947291580697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291582274","data":{"timestamp":" 947291582274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291590103","data":{"timestamp":" 947291590103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291590784","data":{"timestamp":" 947291590784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291590891","data":{"timestamp":" 947291590891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" fe19682b-3482-42cd-a241-cb2ccdaff19b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291609744","data":{"timestamp":" 947291609744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-ch-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291620243","data":{"timestamp":" 947291620243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-ch-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291624977","data":{"timestamp":" 947291624977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_d-n-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291629064","data":{"timestamp":" 947291629064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_w-s-n"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291632058","data":{"timestamp":" 947291632058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-n-s"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291635046","data":{"timestamp":" 947291635046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_g-f-n"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291641269","data":{"timestamp":" 947291641269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_g-f-n"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291645298","data":{"timestamp":" 947291645297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-y-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291651394","data":{"timestamp":" 947291651394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-y-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291655975","data":{"timestamp":" 947291655975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_f-n-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291660206","data":{"timestamp":" 947291660206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_j-n-d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291664071","data":{"timestamp":" 947291664071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-u-v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291667459","data":{"timestamp":" 947291667459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-k-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291673234","data":{"timestamp":" 947291673234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" c67dc1d1-82ee-4366-a2e0-39e7583acde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-k-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291693160","data":{"timestamp":" 947291693160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_g-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291698977","data":{"timestamp":" 947291698976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_g-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291702714","data":{"timestamp":" 947291702714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_f-n-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291707884","data":{"timestamp":" 947291707884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_w-s-n"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291712543","data":{"timestamp":" 947291712543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_d-n-p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291716357","data":{"timestamp":" 947291716357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-ch-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291722332","data":{"timestamp":" 947291722331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-u-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291726793","data":{"timestamp":" 947291726793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_j-n-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291733782","data":{"timestamp":" 947291733782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-n-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291740165","data":{"timestamp":" 947291740165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-k-p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291748050","data":{"timestamp":" 947291748050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-y-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291753810","data":{"timestamp":" 947291753810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 6cd69fd3-2484-4f07-82ac-e67e7cea1c8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-y-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291775128","data":{"timestamp":" 947291775128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-h-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291778364","data":{"timestamp":" 947291778364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-ch-v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291782714","data":{"timestamp":" 947291782714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_v-n-p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291788166","data":{"timestamp":" 947291788166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_ch-a-n"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291791914","data":{"timestamp":" 947291791914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_f-s-n"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291796051","data":{"timestamp":" 947291796051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-a-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291799370","data":{"timestamp":" 947291799370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_n-m-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291804012","data":{"timestamp":" 947291804012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_m-n-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291807717","data":{"timestamp":" 947291807717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_e-j-n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291813025","data":{"timestamp":" 947291813025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_z-v-n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291818803","data":{"timestamp":" 947291818801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 03566915-0103-4c26-b338-edb39fb4e7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_n_z-v-n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291848367","data":{"timestamp":" 947291848367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_m_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291854989","data":{"timestamp":" 947291854989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291861567","data":{"timestamp":" 947291861567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291868195","data":{"timestamp":" 947291868195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_n_g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291874790","data":{"timestamp":" 947291874790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_n_l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291881385","data":{"timestamp":" 947291881385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291888820","data":{"timestamp":" 947291888820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291899057","data":{"timestamp":" 947291899057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291905698","data":{"timestamp":" 947291905697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291912307","data":{"timestamp":" 947291912307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_n_j"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291918944","data":{"timestamp":" 947291918944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291926371","data":{"timestamp":" 947291926371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291934263","data":{"timestamp":" 947291934263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 1d9c06f9-cb9c-40ea-9de5-67e4cc399fa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_n_v_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291967388","data":{"timestamp":" 947291967388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_m_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291973983","data":{"timestamp":" 947291973983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291981516","data":{"timestamp":" 947291981516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291991758","data":{"timestamp":" 947291991757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947291998365","data":{"timestamp":" 947291998362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292004978","data":{"timestamp":" 947292004978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_n_g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292011611","data":{"timestamp":" 947292011611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_n_l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292018205","data":{"timestamp":" 947292018204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292025659","data":{"timestamp":" 947292025659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292032268","data":{"timestamp":" 947292032268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292038938","data":{"timestamp":" 947292038937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_n_j"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292045603","data":{"timestamp":" 947292045602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292052244","data":{"timestamp":" 947292052243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_h_n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292060091","data":{"timestamp":" 947292060091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 26ac4ce4-a9e3-4b10-8516-2f42d08d704b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_h_n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292090583","data":{"timestamp":" 947292090583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_m_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292097229","data":{"timestamp":" 947292097228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292103862","data":{"timestamp":" 947292103862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292110502","data":{"timestamp":" 947292110501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_n_g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292117147","data":{"timestamp":" 947292117147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_n_l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292123794","data":{"timestamp":" 947292123794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292130423","data":{"timestamp":" 947292130422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292137073","data":{"timestamp":" 947292137073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_n_j"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292143734","data":{"timestamp":" 947292143734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292150344","data":{"timestamp":" 947292150344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_h_n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292162384","data":{"timestamp":" 947292162384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" 164a29b4-9e3e-4b26-86d8-27ac1f743b45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_h_n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292183467","data":{"timestamp":" 947292183467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292184521","data":{"timestamp":" 947292184521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292188040","data":{"timestamp":" 947292188039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292189108","data":{"timestamp":" 947292189108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292193340","data":{"timestamp":" 947292193338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292194393","data":{"timestamp":" 947292194393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292197947","data":{"timestamp":" 947292197947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292198974","data":{"timestamp":" 947292198974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292206035","data":{"timestamp":" 947292206035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292207119","data":{"timestamp":" 947292207119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292211393","data":{"timestamp":" 947292211393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292212452","data":{"timestamp":" 947292212452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292215070","data":{"timestamp":" 947292215070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292215593","data":{"timestamp":" 947292215593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292216853","data":{"timestamp":" 947292216853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947292216857","data":{"timestamp":" 947292216857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_031812"," gameId":" b4a3658b-564e-4e88-9d8f-e1ee0997a734"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}